Murder. Scandal. Crime. No matter what he was shooting, "The Great
Bernzini" never took sides, he only took pictures... Except once.
The Public Eye is a crime, drama, thriller film directed by Howard Franklin.
A crime photographer gets involved in a conspiracy.
Leon Bernstein, played by Joe Pesci.
Kay Levitz, played by Barbara Hershey.
Sal, played by Stanley Tucci.
Arthur Nabler, played by Jerry Adler.
Spoleto, played by Dominic Chianese.
Officer O'Brien, played by Richard Riehle.
The Public Eye is a 1992 American crime thriller film produced by Sue Baden-Powell and
written and directed by Howard Franklin, starring Joe Pesci and Barbara Hershey.
Stanley Tucci and Richard Schiff appear in supporting roles.
The film is loosely based on New York Daily News photographer Arthur "Weegee"
Fellig, and some of the photos in the film were taken by Fellig.
The tone is emotional and intense.